

# **Profile**

I'm a web developer specializing in the JavaScript programming language and have extended my skills with TypeScript. I have a lot of experience as a Microsoft developer, so I have in-depth knowledge of React, SharePoint, Azure and Microsoft Teams. I know how to use PowerShell to automate and manage these technologies. My skills enable me to design and develop powerful, integrated web applications, specifically tailored to the needs and integrations required.

# **Employment History**

#### Microsoft developer, Netmedia, Saarbrücken

FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Web application developer mastering React, TypeScript, Microsoft SharePoint, Teams, Microsoft Graph, and PowerShell for efficient, collaborative solutions.

#### Fullstack JavaScript Developer, FindQuickly, Sarreguemines

SEPTEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022

Fullstack JavaScript developer proficient in React, Node.js and Express. Expertise in building scalable web applications with a focus on delivering high-quality solutions.

#### Metalworker, Hand Leffer GmbH, Saarbrücken

AUGUST 2011 - JULY 2021

#### Non-commissioned officer, Armée de Terre, Sarrebourg

DECEMBER 2008 - NOVEMBER 2011

# Education

# Web developer internship, FindQuickly, Sarreguemines

FEBRUARY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Learn javascript fullstack development with databases

#### Bachelor's degree, Esecad, Montrouge

SEPTEMBER 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2021

Training web developers

#### **Self-training**

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT

Web applications developer

## A-level commerce, Lycée Simon Lazard, Sarreguemines

SEPTEMBER 2005 - JULY 2008

# **Details**

Puttelange-aux-Lacs
France
+33 6 45 92 26 14
hp.hectorpascal@gmail.com

# Links

My portfolio

LinkedIn

CodeSandBox

<u>CodePen</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

# **Skills**

Sass

**JavaScript** 

TypeScript

React

Microsoft architecture

PowerShell

Node

MySQL

Git

# Languages

French

German

**English** 

# **Hobbies**

Diving Programming Hiking